I saw several different movies about laying a footpath before dealing with my own.
I still managed to find a number of mistakes they did not include in these movies, so
I was going to show a little again what five mistakes I made and which I avoided.
One thing that is easy to miss is to
The chipboard has an upside and a downside.
I don't know what role they play, but it's just as good to do right.
Or take a big step between the rules on such a pile.
It can end badly.
One of the first and most important elements
When you put a footpath, it is to get the first row completely nail.
If it started to skew a bit, in any direction then you get an error coming
to reproduce throughout the floor and you will also have to fight it
Each new line you start with and the error follows
With all the time and you can't get rid of it.
To get the first line straight you can
lace the floor and above all make sure that the short sides are tight against each other.
Are they completely tight so they don't glide anything.